discountramps.com 2010-01-14

# Discount Ramps.com - Privacy Policy

**Discount Ramps.Com LLC** is committed to protecting your privacy.  
This Statement of Privacy applies to Discount Ramps.Com LLC Web site and governs data collection and usage at all Discount Ramps.Com LLC sites and services; it does not apply to other online or offline sites, products or services. Please read the Discount Ramps.Com LLC Statement of Privacy. Discount Ramps.Com LLC is a general audience web site, intended for users of all ages. Personal information of all users is collected, used and disclosed as described in this Statement of Privacy. Discount Ramps.Com LLC is a general audience web site, intended for users of all ages. Personal information of all users is collected, used and disclosed as described in this Statement of Privacy.

Collection of your Personal Information  
As an E-commerce Web site, Discount Ramps.Com LLC collects personal information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Information collected by Discount Ramps.Com LLC is used solely for the purpose of billing and shipping your online purchases. Discount Ramps.Com LLC does not collect any information about your computer hardware and software.

Discount Ramps.Com LLC encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Discount Ramps.Com LLC so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. We are not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Discount Ramps.Com LLC Network of Web sites.

You can browse the Discount Ramps.Com LLC Network of Sites without creating an account, however, you will be asked to create an account when you purchase something in order to take advantage of certain features, such as the "My Account" and other Discount Ramps.Com LLC services. If you choose to not create an account the features will not be available to you.

When contacting the Discount Ramps.Com LLC Customer Service department our friendly staff may request that you confirm certain personal information in order to verify and protect your identity.

Use of your Personal Information  
Discount Ramps.Com LLC and its operational service partners collect and use your personal information to process product orders and deliver the products requested. It is possible that Discount Ramps.Com LLC may also use personal information to inform you of other products or services available from Discount Ramps.Com LLC and its affiliates. Discount Ramps.Com LLC may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Discount Ramps.Com LLC does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Discount Ramps.Com LLC may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your personal information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party.  
We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support, processing transactions, or performing statistical analysis of our services. We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose. 

Discount Ramps.Com LLC does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.  
Discount Ramps.Com LLC may access and/or disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Discount Ramps.Com LLC or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Discount Ramps.Com LLC , including its Web site; or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Discount Ramps.Com LLC or the public.

Personal information collected on this site may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Discount Ramps.Com LLC or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. Discount Ramps.Com LLC abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.

Information we collect on the Discount Ramps.Com LLC and it's Affiliate Sites may be used to enhance your shopping experience in the following ways:

  * To deliver merchandise that you have purchased online or at our facility
  * Register you as a member of Discount Ramps.Com LLC
  * Prevent fraud and bill you for your purchased items
  * Confirm your estimates and orders
  * Respond to your Customer Service & Sales inquiries or requests
  * Communicate great values and featured items to you
  * Locate and stock the products you are searching for
  * Customize your online shopping experience
  * Comply with valid or applicable legal procedures, requirements, regulations or statutes

Control your Personal Information  
Discount Ramps.Com LLC offers its customers choices for the collection, use and sharing of personal information. You may go notify us of your preferences via the Discount Ramps Contact Form. Please be sure to provide complete account information so we can identify you in our records. Alternatively, if you created an account with Discount Ramps.Com LLC you may log in to your account via the "[My Account](http://shopping.netsuite.com/app/site/query/checkoutredirect.nl?c=578694&ext=T&login=T)" area and make adjustments to your personal information online.  
**Note:** You may also stop the delivery of future promotional e-mail from Discount Ramps.Com LLC by responding directly to any email you receive with a request to remove you from the mailing list.

Do not share your Discount Ramps.Com LLC account password with anyone. Other than on the Discount Ramps.Com LLC and it's Affiliate Websites, Discount Ramps.Com LLC will never ask you for your password information.

Security of your Personal Information  
Discount Ramps.Com LLC is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access, that are located in external controlled facilities. When we transmit highly confidential information (such as a credit card number) over the Internet, we protect it through [VeriSign's Payment Service.](https://seal.verisign.com/splash?form_file=fdf/splash.fdf&dn=CHECKOUT.NETSUITE.COM&lang=en&KeepThis=true&TB_iframe=true&height=400&width=600)  

Discount Ramps.Com LLC also utilizes a technology called Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). If your browser is capable of SSL (and most are), your personal information will be automatically encrypted, or encoded, before it is sent through the Internet. The digital certificate and seal that you see on our checkout system is from Verisign, Inc., a leading provider of Internet trust services. When you enter a secure portion of Discount Ramps.Com LLC and it's Affiliates (which is any page containing any of your personal information), an image of a closed lock or a solid key should appear in the bottom bar of your browser window. If you click on this image, a small popup window displaying site security information will appear. This certificate guarantees that your personal information is being transmitted in secure (encrypted) form. Ultimately, your personal information is protected by the password you created when you signed up for an account at Discount Ramps.Com LLC or it's Affiliates (or another password you chose after changing a previous password). Please keep this password confidential. No Customer Service Associate or any other representative of Discount Ramps.Com LLC will ever ask you for your password. The confidentiality of your password is yours to protect. You may change it anytime by going to "[My Account](http://shopping.netsuite.com/app/site/query/checkoutredirect.nl?c=578694&ext=T&login=T)". Log in with your email address and password, then click "Change Email & Password" and enter a new password. 

Cookies and Other Computer Information  
When you visit DiscountRamps.Com LLC or it's Affiliates, you may be assigned a permanent "cookie" (a small text file) to be stored on your computer's hard drive. The purpose of this cookie is to identify you when you visit DiscountRamps.Com LLC or it's Affiliates so that we can enhance and customize your online shopping experience. You can choose to browse on DiscountRamps.Com LLC and it's Affiliates without cookies. However, without these identifier files you will not be able to complete a purchase or take advantage of certain features of the Site. These features include storing your shopping cart for later use and providing a more personalized shopping experience. Each browser is different, so check your browser's "Help" menu to learn how to change your cookie preferences. We also collect certain technical information from your computer each time you request a page during a visit to DiscountRamps.Com LLC or it's Affiliates. This information may include your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your computer's operating system, browser type and the address of a referring website, if any. We collect this information to enhance the quality of your experience during your visit to the Site and will not sell or rent this information to any third parties. We also contract with third parties to provide us with: data collection and reporting services regarding our customers' activities on DiscountRamps.Com LLC or it's Affiliates; tracking and measuring performance of our marketing efforts and your response to our marketing efforts; and the delivery of relevant marketing messages. These third parties may use cookies and Web beacons (1 x 1 pixels), and may receive anonymous information about your browsing and buying activity on the Site. None of your personally identifiable information (such as your name, address, email address, credit card number, etc.) will be received by or shared with these third parties. If you do not want your non-personal information used to serve ads to you, you can change the settings of your browser to reject cookies. Each browser is different, so check your browser's "Help" menu to learn how to change your cookie preferences.

How can I contact DiscountRamps.Com LLC with questions about my privacy?  
If you have questions or comments about the DiscountRamps.Com LLC privacy policy, please contact us in any of the following ways:

Online: Contact Us

By Phone: 888-651-3431 

By Mail:  
DiscountRamps.Com LLC  
760 S. Indiana Avenue  
West Bend, WI 53095 

Changes to the DiscountRamps.Com LLC Privacy Policy Statement  
This Privacy Policy was last updated on May 19, 2009. Discount Ramps.Com LLC will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. If there are material changes to this Statement or in how Discount Ramps.Com LLC will use your personal information, Discount Ramps.Com LLC will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. Discount Ramps.Com LLC encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Discount Ramps.Com LLC is protecting your information.
